<?xml version="1.0"?>

<text>

<h1>Frequently Asked Questions</h1>

<br/><br/>

<h2>What is New Media?</h2>
<br/>
<p>New Media is a multi-disciplinary diploma in the emerging field of electronic communication and art. This program is ideal if you are interested in having a general working knowledge of digital design leading to multiple professional career opportunities.</p>
<p>A New Media Specialist can deliver creative solutions using web interactivity, motion, sound and print. They have the fluency to communicate with everyone on a New Media Team – from a film and video crew, to programmers, to graphic designers to customers.</p>

<br/>

<h2>What can I do in the New Media industry?</h2>
<br/>
<p>As a New Media Specialist you get to bridge the creative and technical world.</p>
<p>You will work with live video and audio. You will learn Flash animation, interactive web design and development. You will learn the power of data base manipulation. You will get to study lots of hard coding: html, css, flash scripting and php.</p>
<p>Using the essential tools of colour theory, typography, sound, motion and interactivity you will help create the content that drives today’s most prominent form of communication.</p>

<br/>

<h2>What is the state of the New Media industry?</h2>
<br/>
<p>Electronic communication and art have burst into prominence on the world stage. British Columbia is an international center point for the field of media art and technology. There is a good market demand from all industries for the high level of creative and technical competence that our graduates possess.</p>

<br/>

<h2>What are the employment outcomes of new grads?</h2>
<br/>
<p>If you are interested in becoming a web designer/developer, a Media Manager, a Free-lancer, Information Architect, a Graphic or Interface Designer, or a Flash Developer, this is the program for you.</p> 

<br/>

<p>At BCIT you are groomed for success with an overview of entrepreneurial preparation, self-promotion, career preparation and how to legally protect your creative objects.</p>
<p>Review our employment outcome yearly report.</p>
</text>